Uh, but we weren't good enough. I do
like the fight of this group, the way
that we handled ourselves in the second
half. Um,
and we had our chances to be able to
close that game out and um, here we are
again in a in a disappointing situation,
but this is a humbling league and um, we
got humbled tonight.
Yeah.
I wish I had an answer. You know, I
thought they had a good week of
preparation. Um, we just didn't have
that bounce in our step. We missing some
guys, but it's no excuse and so um,
you know, we got to be able to figure it
out in a lot of instances. It comes back
to um, you know, our collective. Are we
putting our guys in the right sort of
spots and then ultimately are we
executing and we'll look at it, but uh,
it wasn't good enough as a whole and it
starts with me.
Oh, we're playing. Yeah, they're
playing.
No, they were going to play anyways. We
need to play. We need to play better
football.
Um, so I I you know, I don't know what
the consequences are and in those
different types of things, but um,
we got to play better.
I you know, I I certainly don't think
so. I certainly hope not. Um, you know,
you give them credit. They made the
plays. We didn't. Um,
and I think it's as simple as that. You
know, we can we can you know, look at a
lot of different things. Ultimately it's
my responsibility to have us ready to go
um, and we weren't ready to go from the
jump and that uh, I did think our
special teams was a major step in the
right direction. That was a positive.
Um, I thought the Jared I thought the
blocked kick with the touchdown. Those
are the types of plays you have to make
to get yourself back in the game. We did
that. We were able to get back and tie
it and then we got to get a stop and
then we got to be able to make the plays
that we're capable of making when we do
get the ball back to even give ourselves
a chance to be able to tie it up cuz
there were some opportunities to do
that. Um, but it was too many things to
overcome. We put ourselves behind the
eight ball. So I were sitting here with
the L.
Uh, you know, I I have to go back and
look at it. I mean, you know, we didn't
there were some instances where you
know, we weren't connected up front and
they were able to get some some guys,
you know, kind of free where Matthew was
having to move a little bit quicker. We
had a lot of big plays called back
because of some penalties.
Um, but uh, you have to go back and look
at it.
Yeah, it wasn't his it wasn't his you
know, he's he's a total stud. Um, we
wouldn't be in a lot of the great
situations we're in without him. Uh, but
tonight was a was a night that uh, you
know, he's capable of playing better.
I you know, I I don't look at it. I I
don't attribute that to the road. I
attribute to you know, I just our
overall
I didn't think we played bad against
Seattle. You know, we had our chances.
You know, tonight we didn't play very
well. Um, we gave ourselves a chance to
get back at the you know, in that game
in the second half. You tie it up. You
come back from down 21, but it was too
much to overcome. You give them credit.
They made the plays. We didn't. I make
no excuses.
I do. Yeah, definitely.
I I got to look at it, you know, but
it's something we've emphasized. You
know, Bijan's an unbelievable player. He
had been doing that. Uh, but you give up
a 93-yard touchdown. You know, we we
obviously you know, hate that we turned
the ball over there deep in the
territory. You're thinking we'll be able
to flip the field and and he goes 93
yards and you give him a vertical seam
and um, he's the type of player that can
do that and got to be better.
Okay. Thank you.
Uh, locker room was open.
>> Uh poorly. You know, I obviously didn't
play well enough. Um
nothing they did to be honest with you.
Um same kind of stuff that they've been
doing all year. Just we didn't execute
well enough. I obviously didn't play
well enough and uh
that's what it is.
Yeah, I love playing the game. So,
um
yeah, I'll be ready to go.
Yeah, I mean it's just it boils down to
execution every week, right? Either you
do execute and uh you know, make the
throws um or you don't and you know, I
didn't do that tonight. So, hurt us and
um
you know, we're not able to we're not
able to able to overcome it.
Yep.
Yeah, it was back and forth. Obviously,
Verse made a great play, you know, um
you know, and and blocking that field
goal and and returning it. Um we got a
couple things going on offense in the
second half, but um you know, just
turned it over too many times.
Yeah. Yeah. Like last week or yeah,
yeah, yeah. I'm with you. Yep.
Uh no, I don't think so. You know, I
don't think that was the case um to be
honest with you.
Um you know, we're
and you know, we look at ourselves more
than we'd look at anybody else and and
um you know, we just didn't execute.
Obviously, had some chances. Came up
just short on the first third down of
the game. Um obviously, turned it over
twice.
Uh you know, on on uh some plays and and
they scored on one of them. So, um in
the first half, which just wasn't good
enough.
Uh I'll have to go look at it.
Um not not something I felt really, you
know, uh
overwhelming or anything like that in
game.
Got going a little bit in the second
half, but again, you know, we had the
um you know, short under route to to
Ferg and
um you know, 31 did a great job of
jumping it.
Um
played the sticks and and made a nice
catch. So, that one uh you know, had we
kept going there, you know, it would
have felt like a nice little rhythm in
the second half, but um
you know, really just
um poor decision, I guess, there. You
know, I'm going to go look at it. You
know, fell aggressively to try to get
the first down there. Um
The one down the sideline.
Um
you know, we got our one of our fastest
guys on a on a linebacker. Uh tried to
put it up and and just I think looks
like I left it a little bit short,
maybe.
Um
you know, and then the other one uh you
know, over the middle that that Bates
got. Uh
just got to
burn the ball, you know, not not make a
bad play worse.
Um
you know, tough for me to think about it
right now, to be honest with you. Um I
appreciate the question, understand it,
but
a little bit more focused on, you know,
our team and and just uh letting those
guys down tonight.
Yeah, I mean every week is a is a new
challenge. You know, just because you
play good one week doesn't mean you're
going to play good the next and and vice
versa, you know, so
um just got to out there and and
continue to trust what we've done all
year. Um and then we got to just show up
and make the plays on on game day. You
know, I mean I thought we had a great
week of practice, to be honest with you.
Um and sometimes you go out there and it
doesn't happen. Obviously, um you know,
if I can not hurt us in in the way I did
tonight, um it'll help our team out a
lot. So, just try to do that and and uh
you know, continue to uh you know, build
with a great team.
Yeah, we had some, you know, um
some unfortunate ones. Obviously, we're
able to over overcome the one. Um but
yeah, I mean it's just one of those
deals where
you know, uh you know, we didn't convert
on a fourth down early. Um didn't
convert on the first third down of the
game by whatever it was, a you know, a
half yard and it was just didn't get
into a rhythm. Um you know, obviously,
I'm and turning the ball over myself
didn't didn't help anybody.